# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

#### Personal Details



First and Family Name: Maria Pieroszkiewicz Address: Gilarska St. 67 m.4

03-594 Warszawa

Phone: +48693324767
E-mail: maria.pieroszkiewicz@gmail.com

Website: http://marypieroszkiewicz.com

GitHub: https://github.com/marypieroszkiewicz
LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/marypieroszkiewicz

Date of Birth: 09.05.1985

# ■ Professional summary

Front-End Developer, entry-level Scrum Master. Talented individual with fresh look and desirable character traits shaped by many years of Martial Arts trainings. Endurance in achieving set goals, life-long learning attitude and need to share inborn creativity.

## **■** Professional experience

09.2021 - currently

agile.org.pl

I am a Mentee in the Mentoring: Hub program, whose mentors are: Marek Konderski, Grzegorz Staniak, Michał Januszewski - experienced Scrum Masters and Agile Coaches.

The scope of topics during the weekly meetings:

- discussing topics related to Agile / Scrum
- analyzing real and artificial cases from the life of Scrum team;
- reviewing possible ways to facilitate conflict resolution;
- earning about change and Scrum Master impact as potential change I eader.

04.2020 - currently

m.pire Creative Agency Front-End Developer

· commissioned website projects work on demand

09.2019 - currently

Drop By Drop Creative Agency

Front-End Developer

commissioned website projects work on demand

09.2019 - 02.2020 Rise Creative Agency Front-End Developer

commissioned website projects work on demand

02.2015 - 04.2015 i-Systems

Junior Front-End Developer

commissioned website projects work on demand

04.2013 – 06.2013 Creative Agency Global Performance

Junior Front-End Developer / Web Designer

- webpage maintenance and administration www.sunweb-oferty.pl
- webpage maintenance and administration www.fitcare.ajdi.pl
- graphic design for festive sweater collection section

Since 02.2010

Web Designer/Web Developer/Front End Developer (Freelance) Junior Front-End Developer / Web Designer

- successfully completed 7 projects ensuring customer satisfaction
- analyzed client's goals and requirements
- developed conceptual designs for the websites
- created graphics and cut layouts
- coded HTML / CSS / JS templates or using the content management system Joomla! / WordPress
- provided websites administration support
- ensured technical support and websites SEO

### Clients:

- Biuro Usług Projektowych i Nadzowu Budowlanego '"PROINBUD"
- Kancelaria Radcy Prawnego Anna Richter
- Compleo Terapie Naturalne
- "Geosolis" Pracownia Geologiczna Maciej Bałys
- "EnglishCom" Katarzyna Buch-Gasz

# ■ Additional experience

06.2009 - 12.2017

Śląski Klub Karate "GOLIAT", Katowice, Poland Front-End Developer / Web Designer / Service Administrator

 Designed, implemented and maintained club's website (500+ visitors per day)

### **■** Education

10.2007 – 06.2011 Bachelor Degree (Information Technology)

The Katowice Institute of Information Technologies (Wyższa Szkoła

Technologii Informatycznych) Katowice, Poland

Majors: web design, multimedia and website development

09.2005 – 07.2007 Computer Technician Information Technology and Internet High

School (Szkoła Informatyki i Internetu), Gliwice, Poland

## **■** Further Training

02.2017 - 03.2017	Computer Become Front-End Developer (6-weeks course, certified); Coders Lab, Katowice, Poland
12.2013	JavaScript Basics (2 days); Functionite, Warsaw, Poland
11.2013	Web Design Specialist (4-day course, certified); Compendium Centrum Edukacyjne Spółka z o.o., Katowice, Poland
10.2013	Responsive Web Design for Front-End Developers (1 day); DevMeetings, Cracow, Poland
10.2013	Myths and problems of Agile - Scrum myths (1 day); CodeSprinters, Cracow, Poland

## ■ Skills

#### See the attachment

# ■ Language Skills

English: intermediate B2 Polish: native speaker

## Interests

Professional: agile, scrum, personal development, front-end development, web

development, web design, graphic design, ux/ui, reader of (front-end, web development blogs, .net magaizne, web designer magazine), newest technologies, social media, participating in different industry conferences

and events

Others: martial arts (Kung Fu and Karate – 3<sup>rd</sup> place in OYAMA TOP Puchar Polski

OYAMA PFK competition - semi-knockdown karate, 09.2009), skiing, spiritual growth, cooking in accordance with five elements theory, (dietetics

in traditional chinese medicine), travelling, origami

### ■ References

References available upon request



First and Family Name: Maria Pieroszkiewicz Address: Gilarska St. 67 m.4

03-594 Warszawa

Phone: +48693324767

E-mail: <a href="mailto:maria.pieroszkiewicz@gmail.com">maria.pieroszkiewicz@gmail.com</a>
Website: <a href="http://marypieroszkiewicz.com">http://marypieroszkiewicz.com</a>

GitHub: https://github.com/marypieroszkiewicz
LinkedIn: https://linkedin.com/in/marypieroszkiewicz

Date of Birth: 09.05.1985

Programming:: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript, GSAP, Ajax, RWD, BEM, Parcel, Gulp,

Git, CMS (WordPress), PHP, MySQL

Tools: WebStorm, Visual Studio Code

Jira, Asana, Trello

Adobe (Illustrator, Photoshop, XD)

Figma

Autodesk 3ds Max, Autodesk SketchBook Pro

Operations systems: Mac OS X,

Windows 95/98/NT/2000/XP/2003/Vista/7/10

Linux: Ubuntu, Debian

Others: Computer hardware diagnostics and repair